(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
GO TO VIP ROOM
VIP / CLOSED
OUT / 2025. 07. 16
君に会いたい時だって
Even when I want to see you,
どこか会えない気持ちがある
there are times I feel I cannot meet you.
だけど本当の優しさが
But maybe true kindness
そこにあるかも知れない
is actually found there.
そこにあるかも知れない・・・
Maybe It's Right There...
人混みに揺られてる
Being swayed by the crowd,
どこかに宛があるわけじゃない
it's not like I have a destination.
一人きり歩いても
Even if I walk all alone,
何か解決することじゃない
it doesn't solve anything.
自分が本当望んでる
The feelings that I truly long for
気持ちはきっと
are surely that
これから二人で
the two of us from now on
歩いて行くことさ
will walk together.
君に会いたい時だって
Even when I want to see you,
どこか会えない気持ちがある
there are times I feel I cannot meet you.
だけど本当の優しさが
But maybe true kindness
そこにあるかも知れない
is actually found there.
二人輝いた季節は
The seasons when we both shined
きっとこれからも続いていく
will surely continue from now on.
だから大切な未来に
So, for our precious future,
この想いを残したい
I want to leave these feelings behind.
飽きるまで話しても
Even if we talk until we're tired,
全部分かり合えるわけじゃない
it's not like we'll understand everything.
言葉より伝えたい
More than words, I want to convey
気持ちがこの胸にあふれてる
the feelings overflowing in my heart.
君がいつか探した夢の
The continuation of the dream
続きはきっと
that you once searched for
二人で描いて行こう
let's draw it together.
忘れないで
Please don't forget.
独りきり孤独なようで
Though it seems we're all alone,
みんな何かに悩んでいる
everyone is troubled by something.
すぐには変わらないけれど
Although things won't change immediately,
とにかく信じていたい
I want to believe, regardless.
流した涙拭って
Wiping away the tears I shed,
ずっと君のそばで生きたい
I want to live by your side forever.
いつか振り返った時に
Because when I look back someday,
後悔したくないから
I don't want to have any regrets.
君に...
To you...
会いたいと言いたくて
I wanted to say I want to see you
輝いた季節は
The season that shined
後悔したくないから
Because I don't want to have any regrets
叶わない夢なんて
A dream that won't come true...
簡単に口にはしたくない
is something I don't want to speak of so easily.
諦めた瞬間に
The moment you give up...
自分自身終わらせてるだけ
you're just ending it yourself.
もっと単純に感じたい
I want to feel more simply,
君のこといつも
always about you.
素直に笑うよ
I'll smile honestly,
未来へ続いてく
continuing into the future.
君がホントに好きだーって
That I really love you...
いつも心に飾ってたい
I want to keep it in my heart always.
楽しさだけが全てなら
If fun is all that matters...
本当の愛じゃないから
then it isn't real love.
君に 会いたいと言いたくて
I wanted to say I want to see you.
二人輝いた季節は
The season where we both shined...
きっとこれからも続いてく
will surely continue from now on.
だから大切な未来に
So, towards a precious future...
この想い残したい
I want to leave these feelings behind.
君に 会いたいと言いたくて
I wanted to say I want to see you.
二人輝いた季節は
The season where we both shined...
きっとこれからも続いてく
will surely continue from now on.
みんな 6周年ライブに来てくれて アリぺこ！
Everyone, thanks for coming to my 6th anniversary live! Thank you-peko!
そして 大変お待たせしました
And, I'm sorry to have kept you waiting so long.
さー、さー、けどね、みんなに楽しんでもらえるような
Now, now, but I've made this a live performance
ライブになってるぺこだから、是非ともお楽しみに！
that everyone can enjoy, so please definitely look forward to it!
そして、1曲目は『そこにあなたがいるかもしれない』を歌わせてもらったぺこ
And for the first song, I sang "There Might Be You."
ま、っていうことは今回のテーマは、そう！
Well, that means the theme for this time is, yes!
パチスロ第2弾！イェーイ！
Pachislot Part 2! Yay!
当たり演出もね、めちゃめちゃ色々ありますんで
There are also so many different jackpot effects,
是非とも次の曲は何が来るかなーって考えながら楽しんでもらえたら嬉しいぺこ
so I'd be happy if you enjoyed it while wondering what the next song will be.
そして、今回のハッシュタグはこちら！
And here is this time's hashtag!
#兎田ぺこら6周年記念LIVE ぺこなので、たくさんポストしてください！
It's #UsadaPekora6thAnniversaryLIVE, so please post a lot!
ちゅーわけで、そんじゃ早速回していくかー！よいしょっと
So then, let's get right into spinning it! Heave-ho.
あれ？
Huh?
お、始まった
Oh, it started.
運命の一撃！
Strike of Fate!
好機 好機 好機！
Opportunity! Opportunity! Opportunity!
笑うべきだと分かった時は、泣くべきじゃねえぺこ！
When you know it's time to laugh, it's not the time to cry, peko!
運命の...
Strike of...
一撃を、叩き込め！
fate, hammer it in!
3!
2!
1!
ぺこらッシュ、いくぺこー！
Pekora Rush, let's go peko!
咲かすか
To bloom or...
枯らすか
...to wither?
現在
Now...
燃えるように陽が沈む
The sun sets as if it were burning
歯車が回る
The gears turn
ラッパが鳴れば着火
When the trumpet sounds, ignition
様々 待った無しの物語
Various stories with no time to wait
発車
Departure
バラバラ 滑車ガラガラ
Scattered, pulleys rattling
真っ赤な過去が追いかける
A red past is chasing
道化師の笑み
The clown's smile
仮面の裏側
On the other side of the mask
どう消しても消えない
No matter how you try to erase them...
傷が痛んでも
...they won't disappear even if scarred
咲かすか
To bloom or...
枯らすか
...to wither?
現在
Now...
燃えるように陽が沈む
The sun sets as if it were burning
真夜中の深い孤独から
From the deep loneliness of midnight...
繰り出す
...stepping out
微かに響く鐘が
The bell that rings faintly...
陰る日々の道標
...is a guide for the darkening days
音の鳴る先へ
Towards the place where the sound leads
ラッパが鳴れば
When the trumpet sounds...
ジャッカワラワラ
...jack-a-wara-wara
待った無しの 演目の応酬
An exchange of performances with no time to wait
真っ赤な幕の
Of the red curtain...
まだかまだか まさかさま
...is it not yet? Upside down...
まっさかさま 突っ向こうに
...headlong into the other side
足を掴まれ 奈落の底まで
My feet are grabbed, down to the bottom of hell
愛想も忘れて 息もできない
Forgetting even smiles, unable to breathe
咲かすか
To bloom or...
枯らすか
...to wither?
現在
Now...
眠るように目を閉じる
Closing my eyes as if to sleep
身体中巡る猛毒から
From the deadly poison coursing through me...
逃げ出す
...I escape
微かに響く鐘に
To the bell that rings faintly...
耳を澄ませ生きるのか
...will I listen and live?
どちらか選べ
Choose one
さあ
Now
快感を罪のように
Pleasure, like a sin...
未来だけ思えばいい
...I only need to think of the future
過去のボロ 焼き捨てた
I've burnt away the rags of the past
咲かすか
To bloom or...
枯らすか
...to wither?
現在
Now...
燃えるように陽が沈む
The sun sets as if it were burning
真夜中の深い孤独から
From the deep loneliness of midnight...
繰り出す
...stepping out
運命が壊れるような声で叫べ
Shout with a voice that could break fate
始まりの合図
The signal for the beginning
幕開けさ 舞って踊るさ
It's the opening; I'll dance and prance
最期には涙流す
I'll shed tears at the very end...
だから今は
...so for now...
耐えて進む
I'll endure and move forward
幕が下りるその時まで
Until the moment the curtain falls...
まだ絶えず
...still, without ceasing...
歯車が回る
the gears turn
究極Vモンキー！！
Ultimate V-Monkey!!
何かをするのに
To do something...
理由なんかいらないね
...you don't need a reason, do you?
熱くなるよ
It's getting hot
君を見ているだけで
Even if I'm just looking at you
戦っているのよ
I'm fighting
期待はどんな時でも
Expectations, no matter the time
もつれて
Entangled
迷い込む
Getting lost
イチかバチか
It's do or die
夢に向かい
Towards my dreams
加速する
Accelerating
ココロが止まらない
My heart won't stop
感じてる
I can feel it
悩み多き日常のターンに
In the turn of a daily life full of worries
君といる時の
When I'm with you
自分が一番好きだよ
I love myself the most
ココロはとまらない
My heart won't stop
光の中
In the light
七色の水しぶきあげて
Kicking up rainbow-colored sprays of water
新しい明日の風に向かい
Facing the wind of a new tomorrow
走り出そうよ
Let's start running
二人きりで
Just the two of us
逢いたい気持ちが
The feeling of wanting to see you
ため息に
Into a sigh
溶けてゆく
Dissolves
寂しいよ
I'm lonely
すぐそばにいてくれた
You were right there by my side
泣き出しそうになった時
When I was about to burst into tears
気づかないふりしてくれたね
You pretended not to notice
重ねる唇から
From our touching lips
こぼれる
Spilling out
切なさも 愛しさも
Both sadness and love
ココロが止まらない
My heart won't stop
感じてる
I can feel it
もっとすべてを変えてみたい
I want to try changing everything more
願った奇跡が
The miracle I wished for
こんなにも近くにあったよ
Was right here this close
ココロは止まらない
My heart won't stop
通り過ぎた
Passed by
夏の匂い懐かしいね
The smell of summer is nostalgic
君を好きになってから
Ever since I fell in love with you
前より寂しがり屋に
More than before, I've become
になってしまった
A lonely soul
こわいものはたった一つ
There's only one thing I'm afraid of
君が優しすぎること
That you are just too kind
たそがれが風を止めても
Even if the twilight stops the wind
夢へのブレーキがかからない
I can't put the brakes on my dreams
ココロが止まらない
My heart won't stop
感じてる
I can feel it
きっと答えは一つじゃない
The answer surely isn't just one
君に会うためだけに
Just to meet you
とても優しくなれるよ
I can become so kind
ココロは止まらない
My heart won't stop
月の雫
Dew of the moon
ずっと君を探してた
I've been searching for you all along
同じ時 同じ星見上げて
Looking up at the same time, at the same star
このままきっと
I'm sure that like this
色あせぬように
So that it never fades
リーチ
Reach!
輝くマリンブルー
Shining Marine Blue
やっと出会ったサマータイム
Finally met, summertime
ミラクルマリンパワー
Miracle Marine Power
「せーの」で飛び込もう！
Let's jump in on the count of three!
Go! Go! Let's Go! SEA STORY
太陽さんさん 裸足で
The sun is shining, I'm barefoot...
かけだしていこうビーチへ
let's run to the beach!
トコナツ 冒険
Midsummer adventure,
見つけにいこう 海のワンダーランド
let's go find the ocean wonderland!
みんな歌えば (歌おう) イルカがジャンプ (高く)
If everyone sings (Let's sing!), dolphin jumps high (High!)
カニとタコのダンス (ワンツー)
Crab and octopus dance (One, two!)
スペシャルな夢を描こう!
Let's paint a special dream!
輝くマリンブルー
Shining Marine Blue,
やっと出会ったサマータイム
finally met, Summer Time!
ミラクルマリンパワー
Miracle Marine Power,
「せーの」で飛び込もう!
on the count of "one, two," let's dive in!
Go! Go! Let's Go! SEA STORY
海底探検 泳いで
Deep sea exploration, swim and
一緒に遊びにいこうよ
let's go play together!
笑顔が何よりの
A smile is more precious than anything,
たったひとつの宝物だよ
it's the only treasure!
シャチの背中に (乗って) サンゴのトンネル (抜けて)
On the orca's back (Ride it!), through the coral tunnel (Go through!)
クラゲのリズム (ワンツー)
Jellyfish rhythm (One, two!)
始まる夢のステージ!
The dream stage is about to begin!
きらめくマリンスノー
Twinkling Marine Snow,
みんないっしょにEveryday
everyone together everyday!
スペシャルサマーソング
Special summer song,
「せーの」で始めよう!
on the count of "one, two," let's start!
Go! Go! Let's Go! SEA STORY
輝くマリンブルー
Shining Marine Blue,
やっと出会ったサマータイム
finally met, Summer Time!
ミラクルマリンパワー
Miracle Marine Power,
「せーの」で飛び込もう!
on the count of "one, two," let's dive in!
グレート マリンブルー
Great Marine Blue,
水平線のかなたまで
reaching as far as the horizon,
ミラクルマリンパワー
Miracle Marine Power,
「せーの」で飛び込もう!
on the count of "one, two," let's dive in!
Go! Go! Let's Go! SEA STORY
真っ赤な薔薇は あいつの唇
The deep red roses are like her lips,
やさしく抱きしめて くれとねだる
begging to be embraced gently.
瞳の奥に 獲物を映して
Reflecting the prey in the depths of those eyes,
寂しく問いかける 愛の在りか
lonely, asking where love can be found.
男には 自分の世界がある
A man has his own world;
たとえるなら
if I were to compare it,
空をかける ひとすじの流れ星
to a shooting star that races across the sky.
孤独な笑みを 夕陽にさらして
Exposing a lonely smile to the evening sun,
背中で泣いている 男の美学
the aesthetics of a man crying with his back turned.
背中で泣いている
Crying with your back turned,
男の美学
A man's aesthetic.
真珠の色は あいつのまなざし
The color of pearls is her gaze,
遥かな幸せを
a distant happiness
夢に描く
painted in a dream.
いためることを
Fearing so much
恐れるあまりに
that I might hurt her,
冷たく突き放す
I coldly push her away,
愛もあるさ
there's that kind of love too.
男には 自分の世界がある
A man has his own world.
たとえるなら
If I were to compare it,
風をはらい
clearing the wind,
荒れ狂う稲光
a raging lightning bolt.
都会の闇に
Into the darkness of the city,
体を溶かして
melting my body,
口笛吹いてる
whistling,
男の美学
a man's aesthetic.
Amazing grace
how sweet the sound
That saved a wretch
like me
乙女アタック 突入!
Otome Attack, start!
いざ勝負!
Let's battle!
いくぺこ!
Here I go, peko!
いざ勝負!
Let's battle!
勝利! 楽勝ぺこ〜!
Victory! That was easy, peko~!
夜を彷徨う影が
Shadows wandering the night
光を奪おうと吠える
Howl to snatch away the light
罪深き羊たち
O sinful sheep,
来なさい 容赦はしません
Come here, I will show no mercy
守るべき正義のため
For the sake of justice to protect,
優しい心のため
for the sake of a gentle heart,
どんなに傷つこうと 祈りましょう
no matter how hurt we get, let us pray.
御心に 添う命かけて
Risking our lives to follow the divine will,
視線を 戦場、向けて
turning our gaze toward the battlefield,
信じた仲間たちと
with the comrades we believed in,
この手に宿る力 信じて
believing in the power dwelling in these hands.
狂い咲けよ 咲き誇れ 闘志の華よ
Bloom wildly, bloom proudly, flower of fighting spirit
戦の地に降り立つ夢
A dream descending upon the land of battle
大輪の炎 闇を 蹴散らして
Large flames scattering the darkness
勇気と熱を盾に 掴め
Grab it, with courage and heat as your shield
連れて行こう 辿り着く金色の空
I'll take you there, to the golden sky we reach
笑顔を育む大地へ
To the land that nurtures smiles
夜はいずれ去り 朝が訪れる
The night will eventually pass, and morning will visit
全てを越えて 君の愛 叶う
Transcending everything, your love will come true
星の巡りを辿り
Following the movement of the stars
手にした希望の十字
The cross of hope in hand
後悔などしないわ
I won't have any regrets
許しは私が与える
I will grant forgiveness
発条仕掛けの意 踊れ影よ
Clockwork intention, dance, oh shadow
光が導きし舞 遊びはおしまい
A dance guided by light, play time is over
大胆不敵な場所 命生まれる楽園
A fearless place, a paradise where life is born
勝利の扉開く鍵
The key that opens the door to victory
さぁ 共に行きましょう
Now, let's go together
正義は必ず勝つ いつでも
Justice will always win, always
空を渡る 溢れだし燃える想いが
Thoughts overflowing and burning, crossing the sky
鮮やかに彩る虹へ
Into a rainbow colored vividly
伸ばす手と手 瞳を交わして
Reaching hand to hand, meeting eyes
絆結べば
if we tie a bond
見えてくる新しい明日が
A new tomorrow comes into view
時を越えて 暁の幸せはほら
Transcending time, look, the happiness of dawn
誰の上にも降り注ぐ
Is pouring down on everyone
胸の中を 雨はやがて止み
In my heart, the rain will soon stop
渇きを癒すよ
and heal the thirst
過去を解き放て 君の夢を問う
Release the past, I ask of your dream
貴方と想いを
With you and the thoughts
数えきれないほどの出会いと別れ 重ねて
piling up countless encounters and partings
真実 人は生きる意味を 見つける
Truth... people find the meaning of life
狂い咲けよ 咲き誇れ 闘志の華よ
Bloom wildly, bloom proudly, flower of fighting spirit
戦の地に降り立つ夢
A dream descending upon the land of battle
運命を 大輪の炎 闇を 蹴散らして
Fate... Large flames scattering the darkness
勝利を 勇気と熱を盾に 掴め
Victory... Grab it, with courage and heat as your shield
連れて行こう 辿り着く金色の空
I'll take you there, to the golden sky we reach
笑顔を育む大地へ
To the land that nurtures smiles
祝福が 夜はいずれ去り 朝が訪れる
Blessings... The night will eventually pass, and morning will visit
全てを越えて 君の愛 叶う
Transcending everything, your love will come true
待っていたぞ、ぺこら！
I've been waiting for you, Pekora!
行くぜ、ぺこーら！
Let's go, Pekora!
BATTLE BONUS ゲットだー！
Battle Bonus get!
Welcome to this crazy Time
このイカレた時代へようこそ
Welcome to this crazy age
君は tough boy
You are a tough boy
tough boy tough boy tough boy tough boy
まともな奴ほど feel so bad
The more honest a guy is, the more he'd seem bad
正気でいられるなんて運がイイぜ
You are lucky that you are able to stay sane
You, tough boy
tough boy tough boy tough boy tough boy
時はまさに世紀末
It is now the end of the century
澱んだ街角で僕らは出会った
We met by chance at a sluggish street corner
Keep you burning 駆け抜けて
Keep you burning, run through
この腐敗と自由と暴力のまっただなか
In the midst of this corruption, freedom, and violence
No boy no cry 悲しみは
No boy no cry, sadness
絶望じゃなくて明日のマニフェスト
Is not despair, but a manifesto for tomorrow
We are living, living in the eighties
We still fight, fighting in the eighties
どこもかしこも傷だらけ
Everywhere is covered in wounds
うずくまって泣いていても始まらないから
Because crouching and crying won't change a thing
TOUGH BOY TOUGH BOY TOUGH BOY TOUGH BOY
どっちを向いても feel so sad
Whichever way I look, I feel so sad
だけど死には至らない 気分はどうだい?
But it's not fatal, how are you feeling?
TOUGH BOY TOUGH BOY TOUGH BOY TOUGH BOY
ここは永遠のロックランド
This is the eternal Rock Land
拳を握りしめ 僕らは出会った
With fists clenched, we met
KEEP YOU BURNING 駆け抜けて
KEEP YOU BURNING, run through
この狂気と希望と幻滅の真っただ中
In the midst of this madness, hope, and disillusionment
NO BOY NO CRY 進まなきゃ
NO BOY NO CRY, we must move forward
勢いを増した向かい風の中を
Into the headwind that has gathered strength
WE ARE LIVING, LIVING IN THE EIGHTIES
WE STILL FIGHT, FIGHTING IN THE EIGHTIES
野うさぎ討伐戦 突入!
Wild Rabbit Extermination Battle! Entry!
お前の英雄は超うさぎが勝ってるぺこ!
Your hero is being beaten by the super rabbit, peko!
PUSHぺこ!
PUSH, peko!
ご馳走様です!
Thank you for the meal!
This is the fate that brought us here
Watch my long shot
Feel like I am falling into the flame of lies
Tell me what you want from me
Trying not to step back to where I used to belong
Looking for the escape from pain
I will cross my fingers hoping not to be sacrificed
I'll be there
Get in the way, get ready for the time to come
浮かび上がるシルエット 追いかけて
Chasing the silhouette that emerges
Don't down the reason why I'm standing here alone
Maybe it's already too late to regain
お前が次第で掲げた希望を 無くさないで
Don't lose the hope you've held high; it all depends on you
I could
What if I could write my wrongs and save you from the pain
It's not enough
It's not enough for me to break the rule upon this world
I will never gonna leave you
Never wanna lose you
We'll make it in the end
Not backing down for real
I won't trace someone else's life
I know who I am
Blame me if I mess up anything
Take the risk of everything
Justify this cruel world
我がままにして
Doing as I please...
叫び声
with a scream,
飲み込まれてく
being swallowed up,
影を残して
leaving behind a shadow.
I will cross my fingers
Hoping not to be sacrificed
Just to stand there
And keep the others from being lonely
Get it, the burning
Get ready for the time to come
浮かび上がるシルエットを追いかけ
Chasing the silhouette that rises up...
Wait
And don't be afraid to be yourself
It's all you
何度だっていいんだ
It doesn't matter how many times,
覚悟してんだ
I'm prepared.
全て
Everything...
守ると決めたよ
I've decided to protect it all,
君がいるから
because you are here.
絡み合う未来を
The intertwining future,
この手で
with these hands,
変えてみせるとした
I'll show you I can change it.
すべきことは
What I must do,
分かっているから
I already know.
Take this pain away from me
この胸の鼓動に乗せて
On the heartbeat of this chest.
There's no way I can fail
見届けて欲しいと 願った
I prayed for you to witness it.
強欲はー
Greed is—
強欲だ
Greed!
超強欲 BONUS
SUPER GREED BONUS
Jot down the reason why I'm standing near alone
Maybe it's already too late to regain
運命として
As my fate,
掲げた火を
the fire I raised,
なくさないで
don't let it go out.
Brace yourself don't forget this is your fate
What if I could right my wrongs
And save you from the pain
It's not enough
It's not enough for me to break
The rule of our small world
I will never gonna leave you
Never wanna lose you
I'll make it in the end
Not backing down for real
I won't trade someone else's life
I know who I am
待っていたのはこの瞬間
The moment I've been waiting for!
BONUS確定ぺこ！
BONUS confirmed, peko!
虹色のフリューゲル
Rainbow-colored Flügel
聞こえますか…？
Can you hear it...?
奏で広がる詩
The spreading music
天に解き放て
Let it ring out to the heavens!
聞こえますか…？
Can you hear it...?
命始まる脈動
The pulse of beginning life
愛を突き上げて
Raising up our love!
遥か彼方
Far, far away,
星が音楽となったあの日
that day the stars became music.
風は凪いで
The wind fell still,
笑い やがて
and then, smiling,
伝え紡ぐ鼓動を
the heartbeat we pass on...
歌にした
...we turned into a song.
そして
And then,
夢は開くよ
dreams will open up,
見たことない世界の果て
to the ends of a world never seen before.
Yes, just believe!
神様も知らない
Even God doesn't know,
ヒカリで歴史を創ろう
let's create history with light.
不死なる炎
An immortal flame,
未来照らす
illuminating the future.
一緒に飛ばないか
Let's fly together, won't we?
Just be 涙で濡れたハネ
Just 'be', tears are dancing wings
重くて羽ばたけない日々は WISH
Heavy, cannot spread wings, the days of WISH
その右手に添えよう
In that right hand, let's add
描くチカラを
the power to draw.
鳥のように 羽ばたき合うよ Singing heart
Like a bird, fluttering together, singing heart.
いつの日にか分かる時が来るから
Because the time when you'll understand will come someday
ずっと忘れない
I will never forget.
その時には心のあるがままに
At that time, just as your heart feels,
笑顔忘れない
I won't forget my smile.
言葉なんていらない まだ見ぬ地平の先
I don't need any words, beyond the horizon yet unseen,
強く強く結んで繋ぎ合う
tying and connecting them strongly, strongly.
ハーモニー舞う 七色の翼
Harmonies dance on the seven-colored wings.
そして生きる今を
And the present we live in...
見たことない明日の先へ
beyond the tomorrow we've never seen before.
Yes, just believe 千年後の今日も
Yes, just believe, even on this day a thousand years from now,
生まれ変わって歌いたい
I want to be reborn and sing.
暖かいよ この温もり
It's warm, this warmth,
絶対離さない
I will never let go.
Just be 運命なんてない
Just 'be', there is no such thing as fate,
物語は自分にある
the story lies within yourself.
逃げ出したくなったら
When you feel like running away,
宇宙を見上げよう
let's look up at the universe.
勇気こそが輝くんだよ Singing star
Courage is what truly shines, singing star.
遥か星が音楽となったあの日
That day when the distant stars became music,
多分共に出会い響き
perhaps we met and resonated together,
神話のひとつのように
just like one of the myths.
紡いだ何も怖くないよ
What we spun, I'm not afraid of anything,
見たことない世界の果てへ
to the ends of a world we've never seen.
Yes, just believe
神様も知らない
not even God knows.
ヒカリで歴史を創ろう
Let's create history with light.
不死なる太陽 未来照らす
The immortal sun illuminates the future.
一緒に飛ばないか？
Won't you fly with me?
Just be 涙で濡れたハネ
Just 'be', tears are dancing wings
重くて羽ばたけない日々は WISH
Heavy, cannot spread wings, the days of WISH
旋律は溶け合って
Melodies melt together
シンフォニーへと
into a symphony.
鳥のように 羽ばたき合うよ Singing heart
Like a bird, fluttering together, singing heart.
虹はかかる
A rainbow appears,
すべては夢と共に
everything together with our dreams.
野うさぎ剣を押し込め！
Push in the Nousagi Sword!
行け 疾風のごとく
Go, like the gale
宿命の剣士よ
Oh, fated swordsman
闇にまぎれて
Hiding in the darkness...
何故 戦うのか
Why do you fight?
それは剣に聞け
Ask the sword.
正義だとか 愛など
Justice or love...
俺は追いかけない
I don't chase after them.
闇に生まれ 闇に忍び
Born in darkness, hiding in darkness,
闇を切り裂く
Cutting through the darkness.
遥かな 古から
From the distant past,
受け継いだ
Inherited...
使命だから
Because it's my mission.
行け！ 疾風のごとく
Go! Like a gale.
魔戒の剣士よ
O, Makai swordsman.
月満つる夜に
On a night with a full moon,
金色になれ
Become golden.
雄々しき姿の
A brave figure,
孤独な戦士よ
O, lonely warrior.
魂を込めた
With all my soul,
怒りの刃 たたきつけて
Strike with the blade of rage.
時代に輝け
Shine in this era.
牙狼！
Garo!
いつの日か おまえに
Someday, I want you
分かってほしい
to understand...
戦いだけに生きた
Of the heart of me,
俺の胸のうちを
who lived only for battle.
愛にはぐれ 愛を憎み
Losing love, hating love,
愛を求める
seeking love.
わずかな 安らぎさえ
Even the slightest peace,
打ち捨てた
I've cast away.
誓いだけど
It's a vow, though.
立て！ 修羅のごとく
Stand! Like an asura.
魔戒の剣士よ
O, Makai swordsman.
運命の歌の
Of the song of fate,
命ずるままに
as it commands.
月夜に輝く
Shining in the moonlight,
孤高の戦士よ
O, solitary warrior.
迫り来る影を
The shadows drawing near,
一網打尽 叩き斬って
Cut them down in one fell swoop.
気高く吼えろ
Roar with nobility.
牙狼！
Garo!
行け！ 疾風のごとく
Go! Like a gale.
魔戒の剣士よ
O, Makai swordsman.
月満つる夜に
On a night with a full moon,
金色になれ
Become golden.
雄々しき姿の
A brave figure,
孤独な戦士よ
O, lonely warrior.
魂を込めた
With all my soul,
怒りの刃 たたきつけて
Strike with the blade of rage.
時代に輝け
Shine in this era.
牙狼！
Garo!
行け 疾風のごとく
Go, like a gale.
宿命の剣士よ
O, fated swordsman.
闇に光を
Light to the darkness.
警告
Warning
ボーナス、確定
Bonus Confirmed
今度こそ 君だけは 幸せにしてみせるぺこ
This time, I'll make you, and only you, happy, peko.
ボーナス確定
Bonus Confirmed
これが実力ぺこ！
This is my true strength, peko!
悲しい日々が 化石に変わるよ もうすぐ
Those sad days will soon turn into fossils.
あなたのその痛みを 眠りの森へと
I will secretly lead your pain...
ひそやかにみちびいてあげる
...to the forest of sleep.
おやすみ すべてに 一途すぎた迷い子たち
Goodnight, lost children too earnest in everything.
はがゆさが希望に 進化する日まで...
Until the day your impatience evolves into a dream...
生命はまぶしい 朝を待っている
Life is radiant, waiting for the morning.
最後の懺悔も かなわないなら
If even the final confession will not be granted...
いつか時代の夜が明ける
Someday the darkness of this era will break into dawn.
世界よ まぶたを閉じて
World! Close your eyes.
生命は目覚めて 時を紡ぎだす
Life is awakening, weaving time itself.
あなたの証拠を さかのぼるように
As if tracing back the proof of your existence.
そして 光が 胸に届く
And then, the light reaches your heart.
心よ 原始に戻れ
Heart! Return to your origin!
涙の岸辺で ずっとたたずんだ
I stood on the shore of tears for so long...
気持ちを 優しく包むように
...as if gently wrapping those feelings.
秘密の薬が
The secret medicine...
思い出の沖へと 運ぶよ
...carries them to the offing of memories.
おやすみ 汚れていた指も耳も
Goodnight, both your dirty fingers and ears.
この腕の中で もう眠りなさい
Please sleep now within these arms.
生命はまぶしい 朝を待っている
Life is radiant, waiting for the morning.
破れた聖書を 抱きしめるより
Rather than clutching a torn Bible...
いつか時代の夜が明ける
Someday the darkness of this era will break into dawn.
あなたよ 祈りを捨てて
You, cast away your prayers.
生命は目覚めて 時を紡ぎだす
Life is awakening, weaving time itself.
自然のルールに その身をまかせ
Entrust yourself to the laws of nature.
そして 光が 胸に届く
And then, the light reaches your heart.
心よ 原始に戻れ
Heart! Return to your origin!
生命はまぶしい 朝を待っている
Life is radiant, waiting for the morning.
最後の懺悔も かなわないなら
If even the final confession will not be granted...
いつか時代の夜が明ける
Someday the darkness of this era will break into dawn.
世界よ まぶたを閉じて
World! Close your eyes.
生命は目覚めて 時を紡ぎだす
Life is awakening, weaving time itself.
あなたの証拠を さかのぼるように
As if tracing back the proof of your existence.
そして 光が 胸に届く
And then, the light reaches your heart.
心よ 原始に戻れ
Heart! Return to your origin!
ノエル、フレア、マリン、みんな、どこ行っちゃったぺこなのー
Noel, Flare, Marine, everyone, where did you go-peko?
ま、いっか、3期生ならなんとかなるよな、きっと
Well, whatever, I'm sure it'll work out since we're Gen 3.
ということで、ここまでたくさんのゲストのみんなと、たくさんの曲を歌ってきましたがー
Anyway, I've sung many songs with many guests so far...
みんな、楽しんでるー？
Is everyone having fun?
おっとっと、当たりましたかー？
Oops, did I win?
楽しんでくれてますかー？
Are you enjoying yourselves?
最後にもね、一曲ぺこらまた歌いますので、
Lastly, I'll sing one more song,
そちらもお楽しみにということで、ここからはグッズ紹介！
so look forward to that too. And now, for the merchandise introduction!
おっ、ペカった！
Oh, it flashed!
おー？ ということはー？
Oh? Which means...?
来たー！ ペカったー！
It's here! It flashed!
ということで、兎田ぺこら活動6周年記念グッズを紹介するぺこ！
So, I'm going to introduce Usada Pekora's 6th anniversary merchandise, peko!
まず一つ目は、こちらから！ トゥルン！
First up is this one! Ta-da!
ぺこら推し法被！
Pekora-oshi Happi!
こちらは憂姫はぐれ先生に描いていただきました！
This was illustrated by Yuki Hagure-sensei!
もうね、着るだけで推しをアピールできる
Just wearing it lets you show off your oshi...
イベントでも着てきてほしいぺこです！
...and I'd love for you to wear it to events, peko!
めちゃめちゃ可愛い法被ぺこなので、是非ともよろ！
It's a super cute happi, so please check it out!
そして、二つ目は、こちら！ トゥルン！
And the second one is this! Ta-da!
な、な、なんと！ ついにぺこらマミーも写っているグッズが出てしまいました！
Wh-Wh-What?! Finally, merchandise featuring Pekora's Mammy has been released!
こちら、ラバーマットです！
This is a rubber mat!
イラストはひこさんにお願いしております！
The illustration is by Hikosam!
テーマは『カジノ』の兎田ぺこらとぺこらマミーです！
The theme is 'Casino' Usada Pekora and Pekora Mammy!
ついに出てしまった、マミーが！
Mammy has finally made an appearance!
だからね、是非ともぺこらマミー大好きな人も、お手に取ってもらえると嬉しいぺこです！
So I'd be happy if all the Pekora Mammy fans out there could get their hands on one, peko!
そして、ラバーマットがあるということは、三つ目は、こちら！
And since there's a rubber mat, the third one is this!
はい、カードスリーブもちゃんとあるぺこです！
Yes, we have card sleeves too, peko!
60枚入りでね、イラストは先ほどと同じひこさんにお願いしております。
It's a pack of 60, with the illustration by Hikosam again.
なんとこちら、ホロカでも使えますので！
And these can even be used for HoloCae!
是非ともホロカで遊んでる方は使っていただけると嬉しいぺこです！
So I'd be happy if those playing HoloCae would use them, peko!
そして、四つ目は、こちら！
And the fourth one is this!
可愛いね、ぺこーらぬいぐるみキーホルダー！
It's so cute, the Peko-ra plushie keyholder!
カバンにつけてもよし、旅行先に持っていくのもよしの...
Great for attaching to your bag or taking on trips...
持ち運びやすいサイズのぬいぐるみとなってるぺこ！
...it's a plushie that's just the right size for carrying around, peko!
こちら、なんとフルセット購入の特典がございます！
And there's actually a bonus for purchasing the full set!
数量限定で直筆サイン入りポストカードがあります！
There's a limited number of postcards with handwritten signatures!
通常バージョンは箔押し複製サイン入りのポストカードとなっておりまして、
The regular version comes with a postcard with a foil-stamped replica signature,
はぐれ先生の法被のイラストとなっております！
featuring Hagure-sensei's happi illustration!
是非ともじゃんじゃんバリバリ買ってぺこー！
So please go ahead and buy them up, peko!
それでは、最後は何の曲かな？ お楽しみに！
Now then, what's the last song? Look forward to it!
おっ？ あれ？ エラー？
Oh? Huh? An error?
係員をお呼びください
Please call a staff member
ちょっと！ 店員！ ライブできないライブできない！
Wait! Clerk! I can't do the live, I can't do the live!
係員をお呼びください
Please call a staff member
直してちょうだい！
Fix it please!
おい、監視カメラ見えてんだろ！ おーい、どこだどこだ？
Hey, you can see me on the surveillance camera! Hey, where are you?
係員をお呼びください
Please call a staff member
直して早く！ ライブできないぺこだよ！
Fix it fast! I can't do the live, peko!
係員をお呼びください
Please call a staff member
叩いててもダメぺこでしょう！
Tapping it won't help, will it!
叩いて蹴っても直らないだろ！ ちょっと、しっかり！
Tapping and kicking it won't fix it! Hey, come on!
おっ、直った。 あれ？
Oh, it's fixed. Huh?
仮想の世に生まれ 生きること
Born in a virtual world, to live
即ち 戦い、勝つこと
Is to fight and win
時代と戦い 己が宿命と戦い
Fight against the era, fight against one's own fate
己自身に打ち勝つ
Overcome oneself
いつの世も大差はなし
In any age, there is no big difference
人の生き様が
The way people live
一瞬の煌めきが
The fleeting sparkle
歴史を紡いでいく
Spins history
今こそ胸に刻め
Now, engrave it in your heart
我が生き様を！
My way of life!
戦の炎 灯してみせよう
The flames of war, I shall set them alight
永久に語り継げ
Keep telling it forever
兎田の魂を
The soul of Usada!
Are you ready?
Shall We Dance? 始めよう
Shall We Dance? Let's begin
勝利の祝杯あげる前に
Before raising the victory toast
Relax Your Body 深呼吸
Relax Your Body, take a deep breath
そうすりゃだんだん高まる
Then the tension will gradually rise
Passion, Force
Passion Force
Y.U.K.I.M.U.R.A.
膝もと引き上げたら右手を上げYEAH!
Lift your knees and raise your right hand, YEAH!
Y.U.K.I.M.U.R.A.
まるまるまるまるまる六文銭
Circle, circle, circle, circle, circle, Six Coins
Y.U.K.I.M.U.R.A.
まだまだいけるはずだもっともっともっともっと!
You can still go further, more, more, more, more!
Take A Chance! Take A Chance!
勝利のために
For the sake of victory
Take A Chance! Take A Chance!
Well Done!
SANADA DA DANCE SANADA DA DANCE
日の本一のつわもの
The greatest warrior in all Japan
CHA RA CHA CHA CHA
不惜身命だぜ
Giving it my all with no regrets!
SANADA DA DANCE SANADA DA DANCE
急げ夜が明ける前に
Hurry, before the dawn breaks
CHA RA CHA CHA CHA CHANCE
熱く熱く構えたなら
If you've taken a hot, fiery stance
踊れ！歌え！SANADANCE 戦CISE!
Dance! Sing! SANADANCE SEN CISE!
Wow Wow Wow...
(It's Cypher time)
Close your eyes 瞑想
Close your eyes, meditate
Don't think... Feel
感覚研ぎ澄ませたなら高まる Passion Force
If you sharpen your senses, your Passion Force will rise
Passion Force
Y.U.K.I.M.U.R.A.
フロントキックでツイストかまして視線は下げずにハイ、ポーズ!
Deliver a front kick with a twist, keep your eyes up, and strike a pose!
Y.U.K.I.M.U.R.A.
回って回ってブンブン回って回転スピード増し増し
Spin and spin, spin around rapidly, increasing the rotation speed!
Y.U.K.I.M.U.R.A.
勢いつけてそうだ！もっともっともっともっと！
Build up momentum, that's it! More, more, more, more!
Change the world! Change the world!
Do or Do not
There is no try
SANADA DA DANCE SANADA DA DANCE
ハート燃やして不夜城
Burning my heart in the sleepless castle
CHA RA CHA CHA CHA
断邪不惜身命だぜ
Conquering evil, giving my all with no regrets!
SANADA DA DANCE SANADA DA DANCE
心躍らせるために
In order to make your heart leap with joy
CHA RA CHA CHA CHA CHANCE
熱く熱く構えたなら
If you've taken a hot, fiery stance
走れ！回せ！しゃがめ！伸ばせ！空に叫べ！SANADANCE 戦CISE!
Run! Spin! Crouch! Stretch! Scream to the sky! SANADANCE SEN CISE!
Wow Wow Wow...
苦しい時や辛い時には体動かせよ SANADANCE
When times are hard and painful, move your body! SANADANCE
天上天下唯我独尊みんなで踊ろうぜ SANADANCE
In all heaven and earth, I alone am honored, let's all dance! SANADANCE
Let's Go!
Take A Chance! Change the world!
深呼吸 Ba Hoooooo!
Deep breath, Ba Hoooooo!
Wow Wow Wow...
本日も最終最後の時間まで、兎田ぺこら6周年ライブにお付き合いいただきまして、誠にありがとうございました。
Thank you so much for staying with us until the very end of Usada Pekora's 6th anniversary live today.
はい、ありがとうございました。ありがとうございました。
Yes, thank you very much. Thank you very much.
残念ではございますが、まもなく本日のライブはすべて終了とさせていただきます。
It's unfortunate, but today's live performance will soon be coming to a complete end.
メンバーシップカードをお持ちのお客様にご案内申し上げます。
I have an announcement for customers who have a membership card.
メンバーシップカードをお持ちの方は、この後の10時15分より行われるアンコールライブにもご参加いただけます。
Membership card holders can also participate in the encore live starting at 10:15 PM.
お持ちでない方もまだ間に合いますので、これを機にぜひご加入ください。
For those who don't have one, there's still time, so please take this opportunity to join.
また、グッズ販売のほうもまもなくカートオープンとなります。
Also, merchandise sales will be opening soon.
10時10分より販売となりますので、ご購入をご検討の皆様は販売サイトにてご購入ください。
Sales will start at 10:10 PM, so if you're considering a purchase, please do so on the sales site.
明日、ご案内を申し上げます。
I'll make an announcement for tomorrow.
明日の営業は通常通り夜から配信を行います。
Tomorrow's operations will be as usual, with a stream starting in the evening.
明日も兎田ぺこら、張り切ってまいりますので、ご来店お待ちしております。
Usada Pekora will be in high spirits tomorrow too, so I'll be waiting for your visit.
大変名残惜しくはございますが、本日はこれにてライブ終了とさせていただきます。
It's very hard to say goodbye, but this concludes today's live performance.
最終最後までお付き合いいただきありがとうございました。
Thank you for staying with me until the very end.